{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "She could not but ___ to hear such a sad story.",
            "a": "to weep",
            "b": "weep",
            "c": "weeping",
            "d": "to weeping",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Somebody cannot but do something: used to say that someone has to do something or cannot stop themselves from doing it",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw him ___ out of the gate.",
            "a": "to go",
            "b": "go",
            "c": "to going",
            "d": "went",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Notice/ see/ watch...+ Verb (without to) :you notice /see or watch the whole action \n- Notice/ see/ watch...+ Verb_ing: you notice /see or watch part of the action",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "A magnifying glass will make it ___ larger.",
            "a": "to look",
            "b": "looking",
            "c": "look",
            "d": "looked",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Active voice: Make/let + object + Verb (without to) \n- Passive voice: Be +made/let + To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She does not know ___ to open it with.",
            "a": "how",
            "b": "what",
            "c": "who",
            "d": "whether",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "- Some verbs: ask, decide, explain, forget, know, show, tell, understand, can be followed by a question word such as where/ how/ what/ who/ when or whether + To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was unhappy because her father would not ___ her go to the party.",
            "a": "let",
            "b": "permit",
            "c": "allow",
            "d": "get",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Active voice: Make/let + object + Verb (without to) \n- Passive voice: Be +made/let + To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ordered the room ___ before breakfast.",
            "a": "sweep",
            "b": "to sweep",
            "c": "to be swept",
            "d": "sweeping",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Order + Object + to Verb \n- Passive voice : to Verb- To be part participle",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ___ that he climbed to the top of the tower.",
            "a": "TRUE",
            "b": "easy",
            "c": "dangerous",
            "d": "difficult",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Structure: It's true that S+Object \n- It's easy/dangerous/ difficult for somebody to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ___ for him to finish the work in a day.",
            "a": "FALSE",
            "b": "likely",
            "c": "hard",
            "d": "certain",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- It's hard (for somebody) to do something \n- It's certain/likely that \n- False: meaning is not suitable for this sentence ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was considerate ___ him not to play the violin while the baby was sleeping.",
            "a": "for",
            "b": "of",
            "c": "to",
            "d": "with",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- It's considerated of somebody to do something ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had no idea ___ to go or not.",
            "a": "when",
            "b": "whether",
            "c": "why",
            "d": "which",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Whether ...or not: should or shouldn't do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}